definitivetechnology.com 2018-09-06

# Privacy Policy - Definitive Technology

### Privacy Policy

Definitive Technology, LLC understands that the protection and use of information provided by you to us is very important to you. Definitive Technology is committed to maintaining your privacy. This Privacy Policy Statement sets out our information collection, use, and dissemination practices for definitivetechnology.com (the "Website"). By visiting any part of the Website, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy Statement. Please read this Privacy Policy Statement to understand how Definitive Technology collects, uses, and disseminates information through our Website.

##### What Personal Information About You Does Definitive Technology Collect?

The information we obtain from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your website browsing and shopping experience. Listed below we provide examples of the types of information we gather.

##### Information You Give Us:

We receive and store any information you enter on this Website or give us in any other way. This information may include demographic information and contact information such as names, addresses, phone numbers, fax numbers, and email addresses. You may choose not to provide certain information, however choosing to do so may prevent you from being able to take advantage of many of our Website's features or from conducting transactions.

When you create a Definitive Technology ID, register your products, purchase a product, download Definitive Technology apps, download software updates, or participate in surveys, sweepstakes, contests or functionality offerings related to your Definitive Technology product, we may collect a variety of information, including your name, e-mail address, address, date, and contact preferences. When you share your content with other people, or when you invite others to join you on or in connection with Definitive Technology forums or applications related to Definitive Technology products, Definitive Technology may collect the information you provide and we may use the information you provide to administer those programs.

##### Information Automatically Collected:

Definitive Technology may automatically collect non-personal information and data through the use of Cookies. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that enable our systems to recognize your browser and to enhance your experience using our Website. Through cookies, the Website can recognize repeat users, facilitate your access to and use of the Website, and allow a site to optimize your experience. Examples of the information we may collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; email address; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; and purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other consumers.

The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of our Website's features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.

We may also use a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. The service provider may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our products and services. The service provider may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to show relevant advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please click here.

We may also collect information regarding customer activities on our website or in association with our products.

##### How is Collected Information Used?

We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling your orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, communicating with you, or for any other purpose disclosed at the point of collection.

At times, Definitive Technology may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with Definitive Technology to provide products and services. We may also disclose the information you provide to our subsidiaries and/or affiliates.

##### Protection of Personal Information

When you use some Definitive Technology products, services, or applications or post on Definitive Technology’s forums or social networking service, the personal information you share is visible to others and can be read, collected, or used by them. We are not liable or responsible for the information that you choose to share. Please exercise care when using these features.

##### Location-Based Services

In order to provide location based-services in connection with Definitive Technology’s applications and products, Definitive Technology and our partners and licensees may collect, use, and share precise location data, including real-time geographic location of your product or device. This location data is collected anonymously and does not personally identify you and is used by Definitive Technology and its partners, contractors, and licensees to administer the services.  

##### Does Definitive Technology Share Information?

Definitive Technology does not share your information with others except as outlined below.

  * Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: For certain transactions we work closely with our affiliated businesses to package, ship, and fulfill your order. In other cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. If you choose to opt-in, we may share customer information related to these transactions with such third parties, who may use the information to inform you of their product or service offerings that may be of an interest to you.
  * Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. When you place an order, from time to time we may share your name, email address, mailing address and purchase category information with a few carefully selected marketing partners who may bring you offers of interest. During checkout, you may opt out of receiving marketing information via email.
  * Third party service providers: We may use third parties to provide services in connection with our products, services, or site, and to manage our relationship with you. This may include website hosting and organizations that assist us in our direct marketing activities. Third party processors and providers will be given access only to the information needed to perform their support functions, and are prohibited for using it for other purposes.
  * Protection of Definitive Technology and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Definitive Technology, our parent company or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * Links: Our Website may contain links to third-party websites. Please consult their privacy notices for the privacy practices governing their websites.

##### How Do I Grant Consent?

By visiting our Website, you grant consent for Definitive Technology to collect the information as set out in this Privacy Policy Statement. You may opt in to have your information shared with third parties who may use the information for their own marketing purposes or to provide you with products or services that may be of interest to you.

##### What About Children?

Our Website is a general audience website and is not directed for use by children. It is Definitive Technology's intention that our Website will be used only by persons over age 16. We do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone who is under the age of 16. From time to time, Definitive Technology may offer promotions to consumers age 16 or over and collect data from such persons. If you are under the age of 16, you should not provide any Personal Information to us and you should only use this Website with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Please consult the Terms and Conditions for the eligibility requirements and policies governing those promotions.

##### What About Other Policies and Revisions?

If you choose to visit our Website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy Statement and our Terms of Use which are incorporated herein by reference, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy Statement. We will notify you of any material changes to the Privacy Policy Statement by posting updates on this page. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with this policy and to visit this page frequently for any policy revisions.

##### How You Can Contact Us?

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy Statement, please contact us at [info@definitivetech.com](mailto:info@definitivetech.com) or 410-363-7148.
